videocond2h.com 2017-09-29

# DTH - direct to Home - Videocon d2h satellite TV - DTH Services by Videocon d2h

## d2h  Privacy policy

Videocon d2h is committed to protecting any personal information that the subscriber may furnish to us. A subscriber may visit this site without informing us who he is or revealing any information about himself. Our web servers collect the domain names, not the e-mail addresses of visitors.

There are portions of this site where we may need to collect personal information from the subscriber for a specific purpose. The information collected from the subscriber may include his name, address, telephone, fax number, or e-mail address, etc. This privacy policy is applicable to any personal information, which is given by a subscriber to us through this site and is intended to help the subscriber feel more assured regarding the privacy and security of his personal details. When the subscriber leaves his contact details please note that we are not bound to reply.

This site is not provisioned for children. We do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from or about children, and we do not knowingly market our products or services to children.

When using the site a subscriber may be asked to enter user information. Such user information will only be used for the purposes for which it was collected, for any other purposes specified at the collection point and in accordance with this privacy policy.

By entering the user information, the subscriber accepts that we may retain such user information and that it may be held by us or any third party company which processes it on our behalf.

We shall be entitled to use the subscriber user information for the following purposes:-

  * Requisition of subscriber information by any governmental or semi governmental authorities, courts of law.
  * For market related research, including statistical analysis of user behavior which we may disclose to third parties in de-personalized, aggregated form.
  * For compliance with any requirements imposed on us by law.
  * For sending subscribers periodic communications (this may include e-mail), about features, products and services, events and special offers. Such communications from us may include advertising for third party companies or organizations.
  * For subscriber convenience the subscriber can withdraw consent by replying to the "unsubscribe" link in e-mails from us.

Please also note that we do not disclose subscriber personal information to third parties to enable them to send any direct marketing without prior permission of such subscriber to do so. Security is very important to all of us. All security procedures are in place to protect the confidentiality, integrity and availability of subscriber user information. We maintain strict physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to protect the subscriber’s personal information from unauthorized or inappropriate access. We restrict access to information about the subscriber to those of our employees who need to know the information to respond to subscriber inquiry or request. Employees who misuse personal information are subject to disciplinary action. we will comply with all relevant data protection legislation in relation to the period for which we retain any information the subscriber discloses to us.

We may change this privacy policy from time to time and the subscriber should check these regularly. Use of the Videocon d2h site will be deemed an acceptance of the privacy policy existing at that time.

Any site that a subscriber may connect to from here is not covered by this privacy policy. If any deceptively similar website or a fake website which resembles our website is used by a subscriber then the subscriber shall alone be responsible for any consequences of such usage.

  * The subscriber shall not acquire any right or title to the CPE including any other accessories and shall return the same upon deactivation of his service.
  * The subscriber is aware that the CPE is permitted to be used till such time he continues subscribing to the dth services. In the event the he discontinues subscription of the dth services or his subscription gets terminated due to any reason, he shall be liable to return the CPE to the company without any resistance or objection.
  * CPE shall always remain the property of the company and the subscriber shall only have a limited right to use the same for accessing dth services during the period of such contracted period.
  * The subscriber shall render all assistance and cooperate with the company and its authorized representatives at the time of any visit by the company personnel or engineer to the subscriber’s premises where the CPE is located
  * The subscriber shall render all assistance and cooperate with the company and its authorized representatives during repossession of the CPE from the subscriber in the event of disconnection of the dth services due to non recharge by the subscriber and/or events as mentioned in clause 11 (j) of the CAF terms and conditions.
  * No transfer and / or shifting of STB is allowed without prior permission of the company.
  * Any transfer / re-location done by the company will be on chargeable basis as per company policy.
  * The subscriber agrees to continue with the service for at least 84 months, hereinafter referred to as “minimum period”.

* * *
